Brother, isn't he...?
The one from Resembool.
Hey! Are you the one who wrecked this village?
Were you planning to do the same to Resembool?
What's your aim?
What did you make with that transmutation circle?
I had a feeling we would meet again.
You rascal. Stop talking nonsense!
Brother!
You're also... a young alchemist.
You have the same eyes as I do.
Brother!
You have no right to stop me.
Crowley!
It's Crowley, right?
It has to be you. I knew it, it's Crowley!
Don't you recognize me? It's me, Arlen!
Crowley!
Crowley...
Wrong.
The Arlen I know is not an old man like you.
What are you saying? Of course I am!
How many decades do you think have passed since then?
You're the one who's wrong! What on earth happened to you?
Crowley!
There he goes again...
He melted away and disappeared.
Looks like it’s over now.
Pull yourself together, Lieutenant Havoc. Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
Could you tell the Colonel to double my hazard pay?
I wasn't told this site would be so dangerous.